<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uk on In which I type semi-literate nonsense into a webpage</title>
    <link>https://vitiate.org/tags/uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uk on In which I type semi-literate nonsense into a webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 22:41:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vitiate.org/tags/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Brexit Britain</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/post-brexit-britain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 22:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/post-brexit-britain/</guid>
      <description>I want to prefix this long diatribe with the disclaimers that I am not an expert on politics, I am not an economist, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even a particularly smart person. For reals.
This will be my second ever political blog posting. I&amp;rsquo;m almost ashamed of myself for doing it. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ve just never felt so compelled to write about things like this before - I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the losing side of every major election I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to vote in and I&amp;rsquo;ve brushed it off with a sigh and just, y&amp;rsquo;know&amp;hellip; got on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referendum-dums</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/referendum-dums/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/referendum-dums/</guid>
      <description>Not normally a political animal, me. I&amp;rsquo;m not someone who&amp;rsquo;ll generally preach either - you vote for whoever, or whatever you want to - I&amp;rsquo;m not here to judge. However, I find myself drawn to write something about this upcoming European Referendum.
Friends, family and co-workers have asked me how I&amp;rsquo;ll vote - which surprises me as people tend to be quite secretive about their political voting habits - like, you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t ask a colleague at the office who they were voting for in a General Election, right?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>