<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on James Sheridan</title>
    <link>https://vitiate.org/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on James Sheridan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 13:33:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vitiate.org/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very British Guide to the US Election - part 3 - Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 13:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_3/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to my Very British Guide to the US Election, where we&amp;rsquo;ve been talking about the machinations of the race for the White House. If you&amp;rsquo;ve missed them, catch parts 1 and 2.
 Today&amp;rsquo;s the day of the Nevada Caucuses, and will be a make-or-break day for some of the remaining candidates. Chief amongst those is probably former Vice-President, Joe Biden. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about Joe.
Joe&amp;rsquo;s campaign is not where his advisors and pundits thought it would be at this early stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very British Guide to the US Election - part 2</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_2/</guid>
      <description>This is Part 2 of my Very British Guide to the US Election. If you missed Part 1, find it here.
 So, now that we&amp;rsquo;ve covered our Civics 101, looking at Congress, the President, voting and the Electoral College, let&amp;rsquo;s start looking at what&amp;rsquo;s actually going to happen this year.
 Donald Trump vs. ?? Presidents can only serve a maximum of two consecutive terms of 4 years, for a total of 8 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very British Guide to the US Election - part 1</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/us_election_part_1/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s officially Election season in the US. I mean, for reals. It feels like it has been looming, ominously, on the horizon here, like a unavoidable future task that will definitely demand your attention - like a tax return, or a leaky roof.
And, it&amp;rsquo;s kind of felt like this since the day of the infamous &amp;ldquo;yuge&amp;rdquo; inauguration, and the rumbling, lengthy sagas of the Robert Mueller report1 and the Impeachment trial2 were just mere distractions before the real task at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Brexit Britain</title>
      <link>https://vitiate.org/post/post-brexit-britain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 22:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitiate.org/post/post-brexit-britain/</guid>
      <description>I want to prefix this long diatribe with the disclaimers that I am not an expert on politics, I am not an economist, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even a particularly smart person. For reals.
 This will be my second ever political blog posting. I&amp;rsquo;m almost ashamed of myself for doing it. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ve just never felt so compelled to write about things like this before - I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the losing side of every major election I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to vote in and I&amp;rsquo;ve brushed it off with a sigh and just, y&amp;rsquo;know&amp;hellip; got on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>